[
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Who led the Israelites out of Egypt?",
    "options": [
      "Moses",
      "Abraham",
      "David",
      "Paul"
    ],
    "answer": "Moses"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Test 1 (R)",
    "options": [
      "Q",
      "R",
      "S",
      "T"
    ],
    "answer": "R"
  },
  {
    "type": "paragraph",
    "question": "Briefly explain the significance of the resurrection of Jesus.",
    "answer": "open-ended"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Who made the heavens?",
    "options": [
      "Moses",
      "Abraham",
      "God",
      "Paul"
    ],
    "answer": "God"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Who is Abraham's first wife?",
    "options": [
      "Hagar",
      "Keturah",
      "Sarah",
      "Ruth"
    ],
    "answer": "Sarah"
  },
  {
    "type": "paragraph",
    "question": "Test A",
    "answer": "open-ended",
    "is_tiebreaker": true
  },
  {
    "type": "paragraph",
    "question": "Test B",
    "answer": "open-ended",
    "is_tiebreaker": true
  },
  {
    "type": "paragraph",
    "question": "Test C",
    "answer": "open-ended",
    "is_tiebreaker": true
  },
  {
    "type": "paragraph",
    "question": "Test D",
    "answer": "open-ended",
    "is_tiebreaker": true
  },

  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Test 2 (V)",
    "options": [
      "U",
      "V",
      "W",
      "X"
    ],
    "answer": "V",
    "is_tiebreaker": true
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Test 3 (Z)",
    "options": [
      "Y",
      "Z",
      "A",
      "B"
    ],
    "answer": "Z",
    "is_tiebreaker": true
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "Test 4 (L)",
    "options": [
      "C",
      "L",
      "E",
      "F"
    ],
    "answer": "L",
    "is_tiebreaker": true
  }
]